Guide to the Medical Center Public Relations records, 1913-1999 RG0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Departmental files, 1947-1999; RG0045 Series 14; 8 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 5, Box 7, Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  - Sacramento, California and Utah Tour, Fall, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Photos and negatives
  - School of Public Health and Health Sciences Chartering Ceremony, Marvin, 06/12/1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SPHHS Dinner (Harorld Hirsh)-Washington Monarch Hotel, 10/15/1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Statue of GW (with Hospital), 1997 ca. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Walter Reed Medical Museum Reception - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Welcome Event for Class of 1998, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Slides-50th year reunion dinner, 04/1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Slides-50th year reunion, Saturday night, 04/1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Slides-Alumni Reunion weekend, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Slides-Alumni Reunion weekend, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Slides-Buildings-Ross Hall, Medical Center, H Street, 1970-1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Slides-Commencement, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Slides-Commencement, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Slides-Commencement, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Slides-Dr. Bruce Rubin in EMI Reading Room, 07/1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Slides-Dr.s Day, Mrs. Jensen, Dr. Klopp, Peter Goodman, 03/30/1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Slides-Disaster Drill, 08/13/1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Slides-Hospital 23rd Street exterior construction, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Slides-Hospital scenes: doctors, nurses, patients, etc., 1968-1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Slides-Gelman Library, 06/1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Slides-GW Navy Contract signing, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Slides-GW statue on Washington Circle, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Slides-Gilbert Stuart Portrait-Ross Hall, Fall, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Slides-Maternity Ward, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Slides-Medical School Construction, Ross Hall, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Slides-Medical School Scenes, 1971-1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Slides-Medical Student Reception, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Slides-Medical Student Registration (1st in new school), Fall, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Slides-Nurses: Cardiology, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Slides-Nursing Fair, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Slides-Nursing Fair, 05/1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Slides-Nursing Shows-Pat Deyampert, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Slides-OB/GYN Black Tie Event, 03/1995 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Slides-OB/GYN Society (Dodek), no smoking employees, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Slides-Staff/faculty, 1970-1990 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Slides-Training of new ICU nurses (by Miss Amigo), 10/05/1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Slides-Visitors from Peoples Republic of China Visit, 10/1972 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Slides-Womens Board Bazaar (E.K. Morris et al), 11/1971 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Plaque: Gift of Emelia B. Eggena In Memory of Dr. Rhodric W. Browne Class of 1905, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Plaque: Presented to The GWU School of Medicine The Class of 1936 In recognition of their fifty years of dedicated and distinguished service, the class of 1986 wishes to express our appreciation for their contributions to medical education and the preservation and advancement of the art of medicine, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Essentials of Gynecologic and Obstetric Endocrinology by Bacchus, Habeen; published Baltimore: University Park Press, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Elegant Parenting How to Do it Right the First Time Strategies for the 21st Century by Gall, John and Beth Gall; published Ann Arbor, Michigan: The General Systemantics Press, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Formula for Fitness Physical, Mental, Spiritual by Hunton, Richard E.; published New Jersey: Fleming H. Revell Company, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - One of A Golden Breed by McCrea, John Weed and Grace Laura McCrea; published 1996 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - The Official Baby-License Exam by Rosenberg, David; published Colorado: House of Toast Publications,1996 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Contact prints, Oversize items in folders
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1993 ca. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Photo, Contact print, Oversize items in folders
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Claude Moore, MD, D. Sci (Hon.), 1892-1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Oversize items in folders
  - Neil Patrick Harris "Doogie Howser, M.D.", 1990 ca. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - GW Medical School Luncheon, 09/1952 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hospital on Washington Circle, 1980 ca. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Loose oversize photo
  - Ross Hall, 1980 ca. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hospital on Washington Circle, 1990 ca. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Ambulatory Care Center, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Original building, 10th and E Sts., N.W. Medical Department of Columbian College, 1825-1844 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ross Hall nearing construction completion, 1973 ca. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - H Street buildings-drawing, Kingsley Gibson, 02/19/1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Loose oversize items
  - GWU School of Medicine and Health Sciences, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Welcome Back GW Medical Alumni Posters, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Loose oversize items, 4 copies
  - Ledger sized guest book used for Alumni Reunion Weekend activities, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Large cartoons of doctors/patients in test tubes, 1940 ca. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- School of Medicine and Health Sciences photographs, 1996-2001; RG0045 Series 15; 3 Linear Feet 2 record center cartons (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes photographs (slides, negatives, proofs and prints) received from the School of Medicine and Health Sciences communications and marketing unit. The subjects include mostly faculty and staff, but also some events such as conferences, and appear to date mostly from the late 1990s into the very early 2000s. Some of the images are partially organized and identified, but many are loose and unidentified